[rock music playing]
CHAPTER 34:
I'M THEIR HOMEROOM TEACHER
[chuckling] The-The States?
Sounds like a nice plan.
Fair enough, though. I heard you got
many offers from many places.
So then, are you going to go study
at a place like Harvard or MIT?
Or are you going to be a professor there?
[chuckles] Uh…
How long does something like that
usually take? A semester?
Is it a year? I mean…
I mean… [sighs]
If it's something that will take long,
I'm wondering if I won't get to see you
in my senior year.
[sighs]
It's late. Go home.
Gosh.
Get home safely, okay?
So when will you be leaving?
[forlorn music playing]
[sighs]
What do you think
about your friend's offer? Na Deul-i's?
[sighs]
So when you have a chance
to go to the States
and do the research you wanna do…
[groans]
[inhales sharply, sighs]
I wonder, why does he have to go
with that lady though?
I guess she really is his girlfriend.
[clicks tongue, sighs]
Yeah, he's human after all.
Of course he'd have a love life.
[sighs]
They'll do research together
in the States.
Just the two of them.
Good for them.
[sighs]
Hold on a second.
If I hadn't found that out today,
when was he going to let us know?
At the end of the year?
Was he going to be like,
"Hey, I'm off to the States."
[sighs]
Whatever.
He doesn't have to tell us anyway.
Whether he leaves or he stays,
that's his life.
[sighs] And I'm just one
of his many students.
EPISODE 11
[indistinct chattering]
[students] Hello.
[student] Hey, hi.
Are only Choi Ji-a and Jenny missing?
-[students] Yes.
-Yes.
Applications
for the career experience program
are open until the end of this week.
Check the group chat
for the announcements,
and if you're interested,
submit an application from to Eun Ha-su.
[students] Okay.
-Make sure you bring them to me.
-[Ha-su] Okay.
-That's all.
-[students] Thank you.
Hey, Choi Ji-a's isn't here again.
What now?
-What if you get more demerits now?
-[sighs]
Do you think something happened to her?
-[Yeong-jae] Like what?
-Ugh, I don't know.
[sighs]
How may I help you?
Hello, ma'am.
My name is Yeo Eui-ju,
-and I'm Ji-a's classmate.
-Oh.
She wasn't in school and I was wondering
if something happened to her.
Well, she isn't here right now.
She's probably working.
Ah.
Do you know where she works by any chance?
Where was it? [puffs air] Uh…
I heard it was a hamburger place.
The one at the intersection
near the hospital.
Ah. Ah, I see.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you for coming by
to see if she's okay.
Goodbye now.
[door opens, closes]
Oh.
Mr. Ga.
Ji-a isn't here right now.
She's out working.
How did you get here?
Last year I saw her write down her address
on a piece of paper.
Why don't you go home? I'll look for her.
No.
I'm sick of doing demerit duty,
and I have to see Ji-a today.
But… [sighs]
-[worker] Ji-a?
-Yes.
-She doesn't work here anymore.
-Huh?
Since when?
Uh, two weeks ago.
No, no, no. Three weeks ago.
Oh, uh, do you by any chance know
where she might be right now?
A ribs restaurant.
I heard she works there
because they pay her a lot more.
-Do you know the name?
-I don't.
I didn't ask.
-Thank you.
[sighs]
I'll go this way,
and you can try that way.
-Let me know if you find her.
-Okay.
[funky pop music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
Oh…
Dang. What… What's wrong with that guy?
Come on now.
What's the matter with you?
Are you nuts?
Hey, you shouldn't drink
just because they offer it to you.
Do they even know you're a high schooler?
They tip me for it.
Wouldn't you do the same?
Hey, come on. Even then…
Ji-a?
Ji-a.
Yeah, we got her. It's her. [laughing]
Today's the day, isn't it?
Right?
I haven't gotten paid yet, though.
-Next time--
-"Next time"?
[laughs]
You told us
the exact same thing last time.
We're not a charity group.
Come on, what's wrong with you?
We need to put food
on the table, all right?
I really don't have money.
-If you don't, then make some, huh?
-Damn.
There's lots of places to work.
Convenience stores, karaokes,
burger joints, bars. No?
The way I see it, dear,
-you're going to find the money no matter…
-Whoa, what are you doing? Stop it.
Are you her friend?
Well, are you?
What? You think we're gonna
do something to her?
We're not bad guys.
And if you're that worried,
you can pay off
your friend's debts for her.
-[laughs]
-Do you have any money, friend?
-Huh?
-Wait, we're scaring her.
Stop it, stop it.
Well then,
how much can you pay us back today?
I swear, I have no money.
-Damn it, are you trying to mess with me?
-What are you doing?
-Stop it! Let go of her!
-You shouldn't do this!
Huh? What the… Damn.
-Ow.
-What the heck?
Who the hell are you?
Well?
I'm their homeroom teacher.
Ah.
-You scared me.
-Damn, you're a teacher, huh?
This is actually better.
Why don't you just pay off her debt
on her behalf then?
You're the ones who did this
to her too, didn't you?
[thug 2] We wouldn't know
anything about that.
-Hey, teach.
-[groans]
This girl right here
borrowed money from us, all right?
Doesn't school teach its students
to pay back what they borrow these days?
[thug 1] Exactly.
How much did she borrow?
How much, you ask? Ha.
It was about 340.
But now, 1,700.
Is that all she has to pay?
-[loan sharks laugh]
-Mr. Ga!
That's right.
Whoa, you're pretty cool, teach, hmm?
-[thug 2] Awesome.
-[thug 1] That's right.
-All right then, here.
-Yeah.
Wire the money to this account.
Can you see it? Okay?
-[phone beeps]
-I just did.
-[thug 1] Oh, you did?
-[thug 2] Did he?
-[thug 1] Great. Uh-huh.
-[thug 2] Great.
Say she's debt free
while I take a video of you.
-On November 10th…
-Yeah.
-…we received $1700 from Choi Ji-a.
-We did.
Since she's debt free,
we will never contact Choi Ji-a again.
-Happy now?
-Happy?
[phone beeps]
Delete her number from your phones now.
-Okay. Choi Ji-a. "Delete number." There.
-Here.
DELETE NUMBER
-[thug 2] Okay?
-[thug 1] Happy now?
Stay away from her for good.
-[chuckles] Yes, sir.
-Got it.
It was an honor to meet you today.
-And if you ever need to take out a loan…
-Yeah.
…call us at this number here.
All right?
-The number's on the business card, okay?
-That's right.
-We'll be waiting.
-We'll give you special treatment.
-Bye-bye.
-We're leaving, Ji-a.
Bye-bye.
Mr. Ga,
I'll pay you back for sure.
I mean it. Even if it takes a long time.
I'll make sure to pay you back.
Forget it.
You just have to stop skipping school,
and do better.
But still…
If you wanna pay me back,
then why don't you help a kid in need?
Later, when you grow up or something.
-What are you doing?
-Huh?
Well…
it'd be good to get a picture
of the evidence.
You seriously love taking pictures
and videos.
Let's go.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Why didn't you report them
after all this time?
One of the shelter kids
was in a similar situation.
She borrowed money from loan sharks
and got harassed for it.
She reported them to the police,
but they raided the shelter
and made a big scene.
So she had to move out
for causing harm
to the other shelter kids.
Oh.
I see now.
So, can you work a bit less from now on?
I can't.
I need the money.
I have to move out of the shelter
next year,
so I need to save at least $3000
for a deposit and rent
just to get by.
Oh.
I see.
[sighs]
CLOUD YOUTH SHELTER
Thank you very much.
Mmm.
Get home safe.
Mmm. I'll see you at school.
[exhales sharply]
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Ji-a told me she couldn't report them
because they could go to the shelter
and make a big scene.
[sighs]
She was afraid.
I didn't think you'd come
all the way here for her.
Other teachers don't even bother
whether she comes to school or not.
I bet you didn't come all the way here
because of demerits.
You were worried about her.
I'm proud of you.
[chuckles]
Anyway, if you decide to go to the States,
is it because, over there,
you can do what you really want?
Well, you know,
just like I love writing novels,
you may have something
you really love too.
Something…
Something that you just can't live
without doing at all.
I'm wondering
if that's why you would leave.
Yes, maybe that's true.
But whatever it is, my priority right now
is teaching you girls
while looking after you
and keeping an eye on all of you.
There is nothing else.
[peaceful music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
[tender music playing]
CHAPTER 35:
WE'LL HELP LIKE YOU'RE FAMILY
[students chattering]
Girls, what's up?
-[student] Jenny!
-I'm back.
[students clamoring]
It's a present for you guys. Enjoy.
-Jenny! Hi!
-Jenny! I missed you so much.
-I'm back. Here you go.
-Hurry, get over here.
[gasps] Thank you.
In Yeonnam, I had to wait in line
for an hour and a half
just to get these cookies.
-That looks so good.
-[chuckling]
Thank you.
-Thanks.
-[gasps]
You're welcome.
[exclaims]
[Dan-ji] Jenny, these are to die for.
-I know! Yum!
-Mm-hmm.
Jenny, I saw you posted so many stories.
They just kept popping up
one after the other.
Went to a lot of places.
From super early in the morning
to late at night.
Aw. My feet hurt so much.
Oh, I got blisters too. Want to see them?
-Oh, um, I don't think that's necessary.
-Uh, no thanks.
-Really.
-Mm-hmm.
[clicks tongue] Your loss.
-Go-ya, come eat with us.
-Mmm. [chuckles]
-Thanks. I'm okay.
-[Jenny] Have some.
-What is it?
-[chuckling nervously]
-Hey, why…
-Jenny.
-[Jenny] She doesn't want it?
-[Dan-ji] Jenny. Uh…
We'll talk in the group chat, okay?
Oh, give us some updates
on where to go in Seoul, okay?
-Like the Han River and…
-Of course.
Oh, oh. Sit down.
[students] Hello.
Mr. Ga!
I'm back from Seoul safe and sound.
-How was it?
-[gasps] It was super fun.
Mr. Ga.
Submit your field trip report
by the end of the week, okay?
Okay.
Time for attendance.
[students] Okay.
[students cheering, applauding]
Okay, watch closely.
Keep your feet shoulder-width apart
and bend your knees slightly.
Use both hands like so
with one on the side.
Now if you just shoot,
it won't go in.
You see the rectangle up there?
You have to aim for that when you shoot…
[students cheering, exclaiming]
-…and you score.
-[students laughing]
[chuckles] Let's do it.
Ha-su.
-There you go.
-[students cheering, exclaiming]
-Way to go!
-Good job!
That was so good.
-[student 1 laughs]
-[student 2] She missed.
Oh, my… [grunts]
-[Gi-jeon] You're silly.
-I'm sorry. [chuckles]
Go-ya.
Don't mess around.
[student laughs] This is crazy.
Oh, wait. Wait.
You have to use one hand, one hand.
Like this.
G-Go-ya's right wrist
is a little bit weak. It's fragile.
So she sprains it often, that's all.
Really?
It's fine. I'll do it.
[Gi-jeon] You can take a break.
Did something happen between you two?
No. Why?
The whole vibe is different from usual.
You aren't smiling.
Go-ya's…
just not feeling good. That's all.
-[Jenny] Ah.
-[Eui-ju chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
Something definitely happened.
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
[shutter clicking]
Whoa.
Crazy. Ji-a's actually rich.
Some fancy-looking people
are escorting Ji-a in a car.
[gasps]
Whoa.
Crazy. Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy.
-[urgent music playing]
-[panting]
Oh! Mr. Ga! Mr. Ga, what do we do?
It's Ji-a. I think those men
from yesterday got her.
-What are you talking about?
-Look. Jenny saw them.
Two men put Ji-a in this car and left.
What do we do? [panting]
-Stay right here. I'll go find her.
-Okay. Wait, huh?
Send me a picture of their car
-and one of their business card.
-Okay.
[groans] Oh, what do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
Think, Eui-ju, think.
[gasps] Mr. Jung.
That's right. Mr. Jung. Mr. Jung.
GOOD CONSCIENCE PAYDAY LOANS
[thug 1] You picked it, right? Huh?
WE'LL HELP LIKE YOU'RE FAMILY
Run Course C three times
and that's a thousand bucks, got it?
-Huh?
-Choi Ji-a.
-Uh…
-Mr. Ga!
No, no, no, no, no. Sit back down.
-[whimpering]
-Holy cow.
Didn't I tell you to stay away from her?
The teacher came all the way here.
[chuckles]
[boss] And who is this?
[thug 1] Oh, her homeroom teacher.
Well, well.
-A teacher's kindness is sky high, huh?
-[laughing]
[thug 2]
Look, we're really sorry about this.
But we did the math,
and it just didn't add up.
Prices have gone up lately.
You know what I mean, right?
So we just had no other choice… [inhales]
-…but to change our interest rates.
-[thug 1] Uh-huh.
It used to be 20% a month,
but we had to switch it to a weekly rate.
While our dear Ji-a wasn't paying,
the interest rate just… [exclaims]
…skyrocketed.
So she's got about $1,700 left to pay.
I already paid it all off.
Mr. Ga, don't listen
to these people, please.
Shut the hell up!
Be quiet!
Anyway, this is how it is, teacher.
If Ji-a can't pay, we'll have no choice
but to have her work part-time
at a nice place
with very pretty ladies, you know?
-Wait, wait.
-Mr. Ga,
don't give any more money to these people.
I'm okay. Don't worry about me
and get out of here.
[metal bats clanging]
Do you have a contract?
Show me the contract she signed.
With those exact terms.
Go on, let's see it.
Huh?
Without it, what's all this based on, huh?
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
I've had a enough of you already.
This place isn't a teacher's office, okay?
-[grunts]
-[Ji-a gasps]
Mr. Ga!
[thug 1] Goodness!
-[laughing]
-What's the matter with you? Huh?
I guess you guys
haven't figured me out yet.
-[thugs chuckling]
-[thug 1] Seriously?
[intrepid music playing]
[tires squeal]
PAYDAY LOANS
This must be it.
Eui-ju, you better wait here.
We'll come back out with them.
-But still, I…
-Wait there.
Won't take long.
[boss] You like jjajangmyeon that much?
-[grunting]
-Yes, boss.
[boss] Look at how much you like it, huh.
Is it good?
[laughing]
[Eui-ju] Mr. Ga! Are you okay?
-[groans]
-Oh, no. Are you okay?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my. Mr. Ga.
What are these beautiful angels
doing here?
What brings such a divine presence
to this humble place?
Did you do that
to our boy right there?
-[laughing]
-Yeah.
[boss] Well, now.
[Eui-ju] Oh, my goodness, Mr. Ga.
[Eui-ju crying]
[rock music playing]